<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>codex</title>
    <link>https://tadaiji.github.io/My_Blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on codex</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>de-de</language>
    <copyright>© {year}</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 00:18:38 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://tadaiji.github.io/My_Blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Core_idea</title>
      <link>https://tadaiji.github.io/My_Blog/blog/core_idea/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 00:18:38 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tadaiji.github.io/My_Blog/blog/core_idea/</guid>
      <description>The core idea The core idea of the project was to let the player play the game in tight spaces and without much effort. To achieve that I wanted the player to expand his arm length with a slider or an system which controls the arm’s length proportionately.
I think VR can be a mainstream technology in the future and we won’t use controllers anymore. So, I wanted to implement the locomotion and interaction methods, so they don’t rely on controllers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Interaction</title>
      <link>https://tadaiji.github.io/My_Blog/blog/interaction/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 00:18:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tadaiji.github.io/My_Blog/blog/interaction/</guid>
      <description>The idea For the interaction I wanted to implement something that uses hand tracking too. I wanted to implement a solution in which you stretch your hand to an object and your hand moves further away from you the longer you stay in this position. For extra clarity while grabbing, your hand should change the size the further it is away from the player. This enables the player to grab objects even when they are further away and still seeing the object clearly.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Locomotion</title>
      <link>https://tadaiji.github.io/My_Blog/blog/locomotion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 00:17:31 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tadaiji.github.io/My_Blog/blog/locomotion/</guid>
      <description>The idea So, for the locomotion technique I thought that the player is using their arms/hands to move, while the further you go down with your hands/controllers the larger your arms get in game. I imagined it something like Hand Walking which can be seen down below. Hand walking These arms are then used to physics based propel/push the player in the desired direction based. And the motion of your hands should be translated into game movement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Random_problems</title>
      <link>https://tadaiji.github.io/My_Blog/blog/random_problems/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 00:16:52 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tadaiji.github.io/My_Blog/blog/random_problems/</guid>
      <description>The course: The course was given to us with the project and here we should implement our techniques. Top view of the course Side view of the course This parkour course had patches of coins on the track and the track wasn’t only straight. For my implementation I added some additional coins to the track, mostly on top of buildings. I also added stairs to one building to give the player something to climb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unity</title>
      <link>https://tadaiji.github.io/My_Blog/blog/unity/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 00:16:16 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tadaiji.github.io/My_Blog/blog/unity/</guid>
      <description>How to install and setup Unity: Setting up Unity is an easy feat in today\’s time, because of the Unity-Hub. The Unity-Hub is a office Unity Software and allows you to install almost any Unity-Build with the necessary options to install all relevant development and deployment methods for the selected Unity-Build. So I went to the Unity Website. From there I clicked on the “Get started” button and could sign up for the student or personal license.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conclusion</title>
      <link>https://tadaiji.github.io/My_Blog/blog/conclusion/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 31 Mar 2023 00:15:12 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tadaiji.github.io/My_Blog/blog/conclusion/</guid>
      <description>My final evaluation As I said in the beginning, I want a solution which you could be played while sitting and with your hands only. Because I had good reference material and an already finished implementation as an example for the locomotion. I wanted a polished experience when moving with the arms. These techniques should also enable embodied interaction in confined spaces so I should measure the “embodiment” and presence while playing.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ignore</title>
      <link>https://tadaiji.github.io/My_Blog/blog/first-week/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 01 Nov 2022 16:38:47 +0100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tadaiji.github.io/My_Blog/blog/first-week/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://tadaiji.github.io/My_Blog/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tadaiji.github.io/My_Blog/about/</guid>
      <description>Work in Progress
This Blog starts as a project for the &amp;ldquo;Interaction in Virtual and Augmented Reality&amp;rdquo; course of the TU-Darmstadt.
For this course we have the task to make a blog about a interactive and locomotion driven virtual reality application/game. So my project blog is sectioned into weeks and they are also linked in the Week overview down below.
My goal for this blog is to start it with his project and grow it as is grow and make new projects.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>My projects</title>
      <link>https://tadaiji.github.io/My_Blog/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://tadaiji.github.io/My_Blog/projects/</guid>
      <description>Gorilla Tag My first project is based on Gorilla Tag. It was developed for the &amp;ldquo;Interaction in Virtual and Augmented Reality&amp;rdquo; course at the TU-Darmstadt. It uses the same physics as gorilla tag, in the form of hands, to propell the player to move around a course and collect coins. There are also some interactions to clear.
Github Link: Github Project
APK Link: APK Project
Walkthrough Link: Walkthrough Short gameplay video Link: Short gameplay vidoe</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
